[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor plays Richard Hoover in the film Little Miss Sunshine?", "correct_answer": "Greg Kinnear", "incorrect_answers": ["Alan Arkin", "Steven  Colbert", "Paul Dano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1997 mockumentary Waiting for Guffman does Mort Guffman ever show up?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This pastas name is the Italian word for little bell. It has fluted, petal-like edges and a hollow center for capturing sauce. It is usually found in a casserole or served with a thick sauce.", "correct_answer": "campanelle", "incorrect_answers": ["ditalini", "elicoidali", "pennette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much money does Elektra King lose in the casino, in The World Is Not Enough?", "correct_answer": "1 Million Dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["0.5 Million Dollars", "0.75 Million Dollars", "2 Million Dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the white tigers scientific name?", "correct_answer": "Panthera tigris", "incorrect_answers": ["Pantha", "Panthera tigis", "Panthera tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Rydell High Scholls football team, featured in the movie Grease?", "correct_answer": "Rangers", "incorrect_answers": ["Rovers", "Raiders", "Tigers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Dax Shepard was born in 1977.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stegosaurus had the strongest front legs in the dinosaur world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the Spanish-American War, what US general commanded a division that led the main attack on San Juan Hill?", "correct_answer": "Jacob Kent", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Truman", "Stephen Decatur", "Teddy Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is irregularly shaped land good to build your home on?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state animal of Colorado and the symbol of Rocky Mountain National Park?", "correct_answer": "Big Horned Sheep", "incorrect_answers": ["Mustang", "White Tailed Deer", "Buffalo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Helium?", "correct_answer": "He", "incorrect_answers": ["Hi", "Hl", "H"]}]